A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1943-1975; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 14.9 Linear feet Boxes 6-22, OV 24-25, FC 26
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Structure" (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
      - John Willenbacher, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Catalog, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Clippings, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Loan Forms and Insurance, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Photographs for Catalog, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Photographs of Exhibition, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Photographs of Exhibition, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Press Release and Exhibition Announcement, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Motion Picture Film of Exhibition Installation, 1966; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) Duplicate; 1 Videocassettes (Digital Betacam) Duplicate (Box 9, Folder 35)
      Videocassettes are duplicate access copies of motion picture film.
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Collage" (1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
      - Marcelo Bonevardi, 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Martha Bourdrez, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Mario Ceroli, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - John Day, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Perle Fine, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Fitzia, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Elias Friedensohn, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Edward Giobbi, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 43)
        Oversized posters housed in OV 24
      - Sita Gomez de Kaneba, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 44)
        Oversized posters housed in OV 23, folder 12.
      - Al Hansen, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Ray Johnson, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 46)
        Contains correspondence and mail art by Ray Johnson.
      - Roy Lichtenstein, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Conrad Marca-Relli, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Richard Merkin, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 49)
        Contains mail art by the artist.
      - Richard Miller, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Armando Morales, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Claes Oldenburg, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - George Ortman, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Alfonso Ossorio, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 54)
        Oversized poster housed in OV 24
      - Paul Pollaro, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - David Porter, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Joe Raffaele, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Eduardo Ramirez, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Robert Rauschenberg, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Larry Rivers, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Sebold, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Harry Soviak, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - Theodoros Stamos, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Paul Tschinkel, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 64)
        Oversized poster in OV 24.
      - Esteban Vicente, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Linda Vi Vona, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Paul Waldman, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Catalog Drafts and Final Catalog, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Lists, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Photographs of Artists, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Photographs of Exhibition, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Traveling Exhibition, American Federation of Arts, 1965-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - "Art in Process IV" (1969-1970), Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
      - Carl Andre, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 76)
      - Lynda Benglis, 1967-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 77)
        Contains the poetry chapbook "Identikit" by Jim Brodey.
      - Mel Bochner, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 78)
        Contains an interview of Bochner conducted by Elayne Varian, found on one sound tape reel with accompanying transcript. Also contains photocopied writings on Bochner's measurement pieces, photographs of the artist with his work, and an open letter of complaint regarding the installation of a work at the New York Cultural Center.
      - Bill Bollinger, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - Rafael Ferrer, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 80)
      - Barry Flanagan, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
      - Eva Hesse, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Robert Morris, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
        Contains installation instructions.
      - Bruce Nauman, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Robert Ryman, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Richard Serra, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Richard Van Buren, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Lawrence Weiner, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
        Contains a copy of the artist's book, Statements (1968)
    - Artist Statements, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Catalog, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Oversized galleys housed in OV 24.
    - Correspondence and Clippings, 1969-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Loan Forms and Insurance, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Research, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Contains photocopy of typed transcript of a discussion involving Carl Andre, Dan Graham, Lawrence Wiener and others. Also contains a photocopy typescript draft of an essay by Dan Graham entitled "Subject Matter I."
    - Research, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Wall Text, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Art in Process V" (1972), Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - Clippings, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Notes and Receipts, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Photographs of Artwork, Sol LeWitt, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Photographs of Installation, Contact Sheets, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Photographs of Installation, Prints, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Photographs of Installation, Prints, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Photographs of Installation, Prints, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - "Art in Series" (1967-1968), Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - Artist Résumés, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Artist Statements, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Clippings, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Oversized clippings in OV 24.
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Letters of Request for Loans, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Notes and Gallery Visitor Count, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Photographs of Artwork, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Writings, Photocopies, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 36)
      Contains a variety of unattributed writings including poetry, descriptions of work, and a photocopy typescript of an essay by Mel Bochner entitled "The Serial Attitude."
    - Writings, Original Works by Dan Graham, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Contains three signed, typescript works including "Discrete Scheme without Memory," "Exclusion Principle," and "Poem."
  - "Art Nouveau" (1969), Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - Catalog and Inserts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Clippings, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, General, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, Thank Yous, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence with Lenders, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence with Lenders, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence with Lenders, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Lists, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Photographs, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Photographs, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Photographs, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 57)
      Oversized photographs in OV 24.
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Supper Dance Records, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - "Artists Select" (1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 10)
      - Leonard Baskin, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - Carlos Basq, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Joe Brainard, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - James Brooks, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Paul Burlin, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Joseph Cornell, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Edwin Dickinson, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - L. Bock Dicosola, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Herbert Ferber, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
      - Balcomb Greene, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Adolph Gottlieb, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Red Grooms, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Chaim Gross, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Philip Guston, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Edward Hill, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Ralph Humphrey, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
        Oversized poster filed in OV 24.
      - Murray Israel, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Gillian Jagger, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Alfred Jensen, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Eddie Johnson, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Joe Jones, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Yayoi Kusama, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Ibram Lassaw, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Richard Lindner, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Richard Lippold, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Seymour Lipton, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Conrad Marca-Relli, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - David Milby, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Robert Motherwell, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Robert Murray, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Louise Nevelson, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Knud Nielsen, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Barnett Newman, 1964, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Alfonso Ossorio, 1962-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Anthony Padovano, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - I. Rice Pereira, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Ad Reinhardt, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Larry Rivers, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Theodore Roszak, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Cornelius Ruhtenberg, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Abby Shahn, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Ben Shahn, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Sewell Sillman, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Raphael Soyer, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Theodoros Stamos, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Pat Steir, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Joan Tausik, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Philipp Weichberger, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Charles Edward Wright, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Andrew Wyeth, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Paul Yakovenko, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Biographies, Master Artists, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Biographies, Young Artists, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Biographies, Not in "Artists Select", circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Catalog, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - General Correspondence, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Lists, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Photographs, Artists and Installation Views, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 50)
      Oversized photograph housed in OV 24.
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Receipts, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - "Artists' Videotape Performances" (1971), Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
    - Budget and Invoices, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Lists, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Notes on Video Installation and Performance, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 58)
      See also correspondence for additional instructions from artists for the installation of their artworks. Oversized notes on Douglas Davis installation housed in OV 24
    - Photographs, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
      - Contact Sheets, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - Negatives, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 60)
        Negatives are duplicates of contact sheets in previous folder.
      - Prints and Transparencies, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - Prints and Transparencies, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Press Releases and Publicity, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 63)
      Oversized Magazine housed in OV 24.
    - Research, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Video Recordings, Archival Resource Key (Box 11)
      - Vito Acconci and Kathy Dillon, "Remote Control", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 11, Folder 65)
        Multi channel closed circuit video performance.
      - Vito Acconci and Kathy Dillon, "Remote Control", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 11, Folder 66)
      - Douglas Davis, "Numbers", 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 11, Folder 67, Item 1)
      - Douglas Davis, "Sequences/Night Video", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 11, Folder 67, Item 2)
        Recorded artifact of interactive video and sound installation.
    - Video Recordings, Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
      - Dan Graham, "Lax/Relax", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Dan Graham, "Roll", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 2, Item 1)
        Multi-channel closed circuit video performance.
      - Les Levine, "Topesthesia", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 2, Item 2)
        Multi channel video and sound installation.
      - Les Levine, "Topesthesia", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Bruce Nauman, "Studio Tape with Two Cameras", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Bruce Nauman, "Studio Tape with Two Cameras", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Michael Netter, "Brigid Polk at the George Washington Hotel", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Eric Siegel, "Psychidelivision II", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Robert Whitman, "Clock", 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videoreels (1/2 inch) (Box 12, Folder 7)
        Recorded artifact of interactive multimedia installation.
  - "Betty Parsons' Private Collection" (1968), Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Catalog, Press Release, and Clippings, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Photograph of Parsons, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Boris Lovet-Lorski: Art Deco Sculpture" (1972-1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - Correspondence and Receipts, 1972-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Loan Forms, Lists, and Insurance, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Photographs and Notes, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "Chance and Choice" (not realized), Correspondence, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - "Colin Greenly: Intangible Sculpture" (1974), Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Grant Documentation, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Insurance and Bills, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Notes and Writings, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Printed Material and Photographs, 1966-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - "Collages by Lee Gatch" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Publicity, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - "Constructivist Tendencies: Mr. and Mrs. George Rickey's Private Collection" (1972), Archival Resource Key (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Lists and Insurance, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Press Release, Clippings, and Research, 1971-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Slides of Artwork, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - "Destruction Art" (1968), Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - Biographies, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Catalog Drafts and Galleys and Final Catalog, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Oversized galleys housed in box 22, folder 4.
    - Clippings, DIAS London, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Oversized clippings housed in OV 24.
    - Clippings, Finch College Museum of Art Exhibition, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, European Artists, 1967-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, European Artists, 1967-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, European Artists, 1967-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, New York, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Destruction Films, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loan Forms and Insurance, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Manifestos, 1965-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Manipulations, A Judson Gallery Publication, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Notes and Research, 1961-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Photographs of Artists Performing, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Oversized photograph in box 22, folder 4.
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Press Releases, Announcements, and Flyers, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Oversized flyer in box 22, folder 4.
    - Receipts and Deliveries, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Symposium Information, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - "Documentation" (1968), Archival Resource Key (Box 13)